# Karen Cai

Web Developer



0433 850 876

lin

✓ karencai.dev@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kc-dev

https://github.com/gigi0310

https://karencai.dev

## SKILLS

# Programming Language & development:

Javascript, Typescript, HTML/CSS/Sass

SQL, MongoDB

NodeJS

### **Libraries & Frameworks**

Bootstrap, jQuery, React, Express

# Tools & Platforms

Git, Heroku, CMS, AWS,

Excel, PowerBI

# Design

Adobe XD, Photoshop

## CERTIFICATION

Certified Practising Accountant, 2014

### **EDUCATION**

## Nov 2022-present | AWS She Builds

**AWS Solution Architect Associate** 

# 2021 | General Assembly

Software Engineering Immersive

## PROFILE

With 7 years of accounting experience, specializing in process improvement, I am well-versed in critical thinking, communications, and project management. In my current career, I am a web developer who enjoys dancing at the intersection of logic and creativity.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## Web Developer (Digital Marketing)

The Good Guys | Oct 2021 - present

- Developing CMS template where required and implement Google Tag
  Management strategies and search engine optimisation by using Handlebars and Node.js
- Writing and maintaining codes to meet content requirements and technical specifications primarily using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery
- Collaborating effectively with content team, merchant analysts and designers in identifying and developing the best digital experiences

#### **Accountant**

Australian Venue Co. | 2016 - 2019 Toll IPEC | 2015-2016 Spotless Group | 2015-2015 Imperium Capital Group | 2012-2014

 Specialised in dealing with full-cycle accounting duties, variance analysis, improving the work process and automating all excel-based accounting procedures.

### PERSONAL PROJECTS

### **Blog App**

- A simple full-stack blog app that performs CRUD functionalities with user verification and authentication system
- Technologies used were Node.js, Express, MySQL, React, SCSS, JavaScript

## **Cryptocurrency Tracker**

- A single page app fetched data from coinGecko API
- Deployed the App on CI/CD Pipeline using Heroku and GitHub Actions
- Technologies used were React, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Jest